Hello friends, I am Keshav Sharma, I
welcome you to my
[Music]
Addon Rider, about its discount,
about its waiting period
and in the last we will talk about its
premium. First of all we will talk
about its unique feature, its
first unique feature is age entry,
we can give this policy to a person between 18 years to 125 years
and what happens in the policies is
that we can give a policy up to 65 years
or a person up to 70 years of age,
in this if
any senior citizen person is 80 years old or
85 years old or 90 years old, we can give this policy to him also.
Next is Infinity Sum Shore, in this you can
take unlimited sum shred, be it 10 lakh
or 50 lakh, 1 crore or 3 crore,
we can take unlimited sum shred in this policy.
Next is Infinity Claim
Amount, inflated claim amount means
that you can take one time unlimited claim,
if you have taken this  You have taken an addon. Next is
your Infinity Complete Bonus in this, whether the
claim comes or not, your 100% claim will keep
increasing every year. If you have taken a sum of Rs. 10 lakh, then
it will become Rs. 20 lakh, next
year it will be Rs. 30 lakh, every year your
claim bonus will keep increasing.
Next is Infinity Assurance. This
Infinity Assurance means that whatever
pre-adjacent diseases we have, there are five types of
pre-adjacent diseases, asthma, diabetes, hypertension,
hypermedia, we can cover these from 31 days itself.
Next under this addon is
Infinity Reset in this. Infinity
Reset means that if you have taken a sum of Rs. 10
lakh, then in the entire policy term,
if the sum shot gets exhausted, then it will keep getting
refilled again. Now we will talk
about its basic features.
First is the entry age,
we can give this policy to a person from 18 years to 125 years
and for children it is 30 years.  We
can give this policy for a year. Next, in this, sum
shot, we
can take sum of 5 lakhs, 75 lakhs, 10 lakhs, 15 lakhs as well, 20 lakhs as
well,
25 lakhs as well, 50 lakhs as well,
1 crore as well,
3 crores and
unlimited sum shot. Next,
in this, there is family floater limit, in this we
can stay for two adults and three children.
Next, in this, room rent,
you will get a single stand AC room in this policy. Next, in this, there is
pre-
hospitalization 90 days pre-hospitalization. This
means that if we are
undergoing treatment somewhere before getting admitted, that is, at a
doctor's place and we take medicine, then
whatever expenses we incur for 90 days before getting admitted,
you will get that in this.
Next, in this,
post-hospitalization 180 days means that
whatever expenses we incur till 180 days after getting discharged.  Whether
the medicine will be used or the doctor
will be a consultant, we will also get it in this. Up to
sum guarantee, complete bonus guarantee, complete bonus
means that your bonus will keep increasing every year from 20 to
80%, if you have
taken a policy of 10 lakhs, then next year it will
increase by 20 to 12 lakhs, and the next
year it will become 14 lakhs, that is,
your bonus will increase by 100% in this. Next
is reset benefit up to 100%,
automatic sum, unlimited time, re benefit
means that if your policy is of 10
lakhs, if you get admitted, it costs 8 lakhs
and next time
your bill comes in it, the company will pay that too up to ₹ lakhs in this.
Next is
day care treatment up to sum, day care
treatment means that if you have
any operation or it is of two or three
hours, like a CAEX operation, you get
discharged after two hours, then that too
is covered for you. Sum stop, next is domus
treatment, domus treatment means this  It happens
that the patient's condition is not good, if
we cannot take him to the hospital, if the
doctor tells him to, we will treat him at home,
that is also covered for you. Sum Sod Next:
Donor expression up to sum. Donor
expression means that if a
person donates any of his kidneys or body parts,
if he donates kidney, that is also
covered in it. Sum Sod Next: Ayush
treatment up to sum. In Ayush treatment, whether it is
homeopathy or Siddha or Unani, that is also
covered. Sum Sod Next: Road
ambulance up to sum. Road ambulance
means that if we take a patient
from home to the hospital, that will also be covered.
Sum Sod Next: Serious diseases are
covered in it, up to Rs 5 lakh is
covered in it. Next: Biota surgery
up to sum shot. The waiting period in this will be
two years. Biota surgery
means that if a person is obese
and gets his treatment done to
reduce his weight, that will also be covered in it.
Treatment will also be covered in this Up to some
sod Next, the
health assistant in this means
that if you have any query related to your health,
you
can get it done through teleconsultant Up to
some sod Next is the wellness program in this
Wellness program means that
you download an app of ICC Lomberd in this,
if you do any activity in it,
whatever point you add in it, then
you will get a discount of 30% on the premium Next next
is the discount or
service product in this If you download the oil tech
care app in this, then
you will get a discount on that as well Next is the
addon rider in this Addon rider means
that by
paying a little amount you can get this policy done
according to your customers The first one
is infinity care Infinity care
means that you
can take unlimited claim in this Suppose your
policy is of 10 lakhs, if your amount comes, the
claim comes to 50 lakhs, or 1 crore,
you can select one time  If yes, then the
company will clear that amount to you.
Next, there is a power booster. Power
booster means that the bonus you will get every year, whether
your claim comes or not,
you will get 100% of your bonus. If your
policy is of 10 lakhs, then the same policy will become
of 20 lakhs, next time it will become 30 lakhs,
40% of your sum will keep increasing every year.
Next, in this, sum start, sum
start means that if there
is any PD, our pre-age DI, there are five types of
PD in which asthma,
hypertension, hypermedia, diabetes,
obesity, these five diseases,
your treatment can start from 31 days after taking the loan.
Next, there is a throat protector. The
non-pebble items in it, gloves,
cotton, silk,
these will also be covered up to the sum shot. Next, there
is an impact protector.
Sum insured increases
with impact. Your sum will keep increasing every
year. Next, in this,
you can also take domestic air ambulance in it, up to the sum. Next, it
depends  You will get accommodation benefit of Rs. 000 per day
for a maximum of 10 days. Next, in room modification, room modification
means that you can upgrade or downgrade this room,
you are
getting a single room if you want. If many
people want to get a sweet room
or a duplex room, then also you
can avail it through this addon. Next, in this addon,
you will get maximum maternity benefit of Rs. 10 per sum up to two lakh. Its
waiting period will be two years.
Next, in this, new born baby
cover is up to 19 days limit plus of sum
misho. Next, in this, you will get vaccination benefit
% sum more maximum 00.
Next, in this, you
can reduce the maternity cover also.
If your mother is two years old, you can make the
waiting period of one year through this addon.
Next, in this, nursing at home
nursing means that if you get a child
from the hospital, if you get a child from a hospital,  You
need a qualified doctor or nurse.
You will get Rs. 000 per day for a maximum of 10 days.
You will also get the money for the nurse's care in this.
Next, in this you will get durable
medical equipment cover up to Rs. 1 lakh,
like a wheel chair. If the doctor
recommends that you need a wheel chair,
you will
get expenses up to Rs. 1 lakh in this. Next, in this you will get Rs. 00 for a complete
visit to the hospital for more than 10 days.
Next, Be
Fit Be Fit means
that you can also take cover for OPD,
physiotherapy, pharmacy, medicine. By
downloading iTech, you
can take an appointment with your doctor for a consultant.
You can also get the medicines that are recommended in this.
Next, in this you will get health checkup
up to Rs. 0.50 or Rs. 000 once a policy year.
You will also get money for health checkup in this.
Next, in this you
can do unlimited tele consultation
through your doctor, whatever you want related to your health.
Whatever problem you have,
you can also take it under this. Next is the
voluntary copay. Voluntary copay
means that your premium will be reduced
if you take the option of 10 per, 20 per,
30 per, 40 per, 50 per, that is, for your 1 lakh,
if you have taken the option of 10 per, then
you will have to pay 0,000 rupees but
your premium will be reduced in this. Next,
in this, network advantage is 10 per discount
on premium and 20 per co-pay of non-
network hospital. If you get
treatment done in a network hospital, then you will
get a 10 per discount on the premium. If you get
treatment done in a non-network hospital,
then you will have to pay 20 per co-pay.
Next, in this, personal accident cover
maximum up to 50 lakhs. You
can opt for this scheme whenever you are up to 65 years of age.
Next, critical injury rider will be
20 per critical injury rider in this, which you
can cover in this cos, that too will be
covered in this. Next  We will talk
about its discounts. The first
discount you will get in this will be on the C bill.
If your C bill is good then
you will get a discount of 15% in it.
Next discount is the wellness program. If you
uncut some points then you will
get a discount of 30% on the premium. Next is the
renewal discount. An emergency renewal
discount means that if your
policy is renewed, if
you renew the policy before 30 days then
you will get a discount of 10% on the premium.
Next is the long term
discount. Long term discount means that if
you purchase a two year policy
or if you purchase two years policy together then you will get a discount of
10% on the second year policy
and if you purchase a 3 year
policy then you will get a discount of 15 years.
Next we will talk about the
waiting period in this. There is a
waiting period of 30 days. If you
cannot get any treatment done in it for 30 days, then
you can get treatment done in it from the 31st day only for
accidental injuries.  Only this is covered, there will be a
waiting period of two years for the specific diseases like myasthenia, cyst, piles,
stone, any operation
related NEET, there will be a waiting period of two years
and for pre-PD pre-assisting
diseases there is a waiting period of 3 years
like BP, sugar, 3 years waiting.
If you have taken addon Jump Start in it, that
means then you can get treatment from 31 days,
next is butted surgery, in this
your waiting period is 2 years and for
maternity cover there is a waiting period of 2 years,
you can also get the maternity cover reduced,
you can get a waiting period of one year in it, in this
we
will talk about premium, there are four types of zones in it,
A zone, B zone, C zone and D. If we
talk about a person whose age
is two adults, one child and age is 35 years and
he takes a sum assured of 10 lakhs, then his
premium will be 901, it is a very low
premium. If you like this plan, then you
want this plan.  If yes then you
can call me on my number 989
9415 You can mail me
at keshma1373@gmail.com Hello.